sw209|Strike Witches 2 #09 - The Bridge to Tomorrow
That weird filler beach episode with the robot statue guardian thing living under the base. This is a long one.
00220|Starting the episode, this shot of Perrine doing things has her completely redrawn;
00334|
00362|
00442|The building on the left has some changes to suggest that it's not completely 2D, and the detail to the roof of the other building is different.
00654|This child looks different;
00730|The background is repositioned and the characters are redone. I think the kid look betters anatomically with her feet lining up with the ground closer, but the details suffer. 
01065|"Look over there! A redraw!"
04077|The Neuroi-of-the-week has a new big red glow around the appropriate red glowy sections.
04171|Perrine's weapon is redrawn at the correct size and she's moved slightly further right;
04398|Alongside the glow, the Neuroi's hexagonal texture is now clearly visible;
04452|
04489|The clouds scroll speed was reduced, and would you look at that colour mixup on poor Miyafuji's outfit.
04499|
04519|
04542|Perrine pops up into this shot earlier.
04565|Once Perrine settles down, you can see fixes to her jacket and eyebrow. Also you can get a good look at how they broke Miyafuji, again.
04632|Damn near everything is changed here, the horizon line, the Neuroi, the character art;
04730|The Neuroi's sliding motion was removed, it's now static in the frame instead of sliding in from the bottom-left;
04874|Miyafuji's shiny new striker was painted wrong and drawn wrong, now upgraded to merely drawn wrong. Also there's a tiny speck of sky between Perrine's weapon and her left arm that they filled in, but shouldn't have;
05073|Repositioned, redrawn, reskyed, usual stuff;
05132|Closeup!
05179|Slower and blurrier zoom-in.
05324|Trude was carrying only one weapon in this shot, so they awkwardly added another one in;
05364|Refined butt;
05374|Refined Trude;
05739|Perrine is now swooping down towards the Neuroi rather than up towards it. Can you swoop up? I'm honestly not sure on the terminology;
05911|One more shot of the Neuroi, before it explodes.
06026|The Neuroi debris is positioned differently and the characters are, again, redrawn from scratch;
06096|Super bold outlines here;
06385|The background is zoomed in, and every single character is redrawn;
06855|Minna's eye's are now pointing to her left rather than straight ahead;
06896|Everyone here is redone too. Perrine exits stage right, revealing;
06927|Shirley, Lynette and Miyafuji;
06970|Lucchini then enters from below the frame;
07035|
07301|Just incase you wanted these;<img src="./images/sw209/sw209stitchA.jpg"/></li><li><img src="./images/sw209/sw209stitchB.jpg"/></li><li>This shot continues to look better;
09126|Shirleys left bicep and left eye are redone, and the shadows are altered;
09437|Lynette's swimsuit has some seam lines, among other things;
09548|The shot moves upwards, revealing her redrawn face and boob-shine highlight;
09598|Sakamoto doing Sakamoto things is less blurry;
09682|The splash when everyone jumps in the ocean is now consistently splash-coloured, whereas before, the central sploosh was much bluer;
10645|This camera tilt is far slower and travels less distance;
10729|
11734|Here's another closeup of Perrine's face;
11893|Up here, Perrine is redrawn;
12029|And down here, too;
12718|Lynette's ponytail's strange ghostly twin has been exorcised.
12786|The shot of them pulling on the chains spins waaay slower. The rotations don't ever sync up, but I don't think there are any drawing differences here.
12875|As they swim off, they're redrawn, again. Here are the highlights;
12917|
12938|
12993|
13269|"Look over there! A flashback!"
14042|Lucchini looks visibly more frustrated;
14153|And Lynette develops some anime eyeshadow;
14439|Looks like they only changed some facial details here and moved the characters a little;
14786|I think Miyafuji's hands looked better before, but everything else is an improvement.
15564|<hr><img src="./images/eyecatch/sw02/sw0209catch.png" title="the best one"/><hr/>Darker French backside in this dream sequence.
16278|Miyafuji and Lynette are redrawn from scratch, while Lucchini and Perrine have some small tweaks;
16433|Lucchini is scaled down and standing back further;
16880|Different camera move here, the blu-ray version speeds up early, goes faster, then stops earlier, while on TV, the camera has a slower constant speed but goes further.
16940|
17017|
17533|I like how they used Miyafuji's original outline as a base to add the seams on her swimsuit in;
18104|At some point in the Blu-ray version of this shot, Lynette blinks for a moment and has her eyes redrawn wider afterwards.
18158|Lynette didn't look towards the camera on TV.
18672|Perrine's arms have a bright highlight added;
18921|There are some small linework and shadow tweaks here;
19135|
19262|The lighting is noticeably brighter, with better looking shadows
21213|Miyafuji and Lynetter are placed higher up, Lucchini and Perrine are moved to the side a little;
21289|
21522|This one isn't backwards, they <abbr title="L,l,lewd.">actually did remove the straps from Luccini's top</abbr>. Besides that, the lighting is brighter;
21740|Perrine's pulling her legs up while holding the ledge above the snake pit;
21829|The lighting on Lucchini is softer and lighter;
21944|Everyone, again, is redrawn;
22843|This zoom was changed to focus on the big pot
23446|The dust from Trude's smashing the pot is retimed and everything is repositioned;
23478|Less vertical blurring here;
23609|Alongside all the redraws, the character animation here is a few frames behind on the Blu-ray.
23749|They forgot to draw in the gruesome bloodstains;
23808|Shirley look forwards rather than remaining in exactly the same pose for a few seconds;
23967|:\ → :D
24010|They decided, correctly, that this shot looks better with Minna and Sakamoto centred;
24237|Minna's eye now lacks a random heavy shadow and the elements of her eye are resized;
24290|<i>The kiss</i> is brand new with various elements altered and fixed.
24361|Shirley looks shocked rather than dumbfounded;
24428|This shot is still centralised.
24542|The tracking animation goes wider, and Sakamoto is now doing a full on Naruto run, which is kinda adorable;
24676|Minna and Erica look much better here;
24750|
25100|They reddened Miyafuji's blush here, <a href="./images/extra/sw209pink.jpg" title="prooof">so it's no longer the exact same shade as Lynette's swimsuit</a>.
25927|The camera movement is shorter and less elaborate;
26929|Luccini waves her arms around more.
27003|Shading improvements to match the previous shot;
27317|The big metal dude Dude has some shading and a big evil cylon eye;
27258|
27430|Perrine jumping out of the way of the giant metal fist happens slightly later
27445|
27456|Heres a good closeup of the shading and texturing differences between the two versions of the statue.
27483|This stylish action pose looks far better and the shot is reframed to better show it;
27649|
27815|The rapier enters the shot earlier;
27849|The camera tilts upwards slower and there's a sweet shine effect added to the rapier as Perrine catches it. Awesome.
27925|The background visible on the left moves ⇧ rather than ⇩.
28012|The big dude pulls arm back further, putting more weight behind the upcoming punch.
28060|I swear I've seen this exact shot somewhere before. Probably a cliché anime shot;
28095|Perrine actually lands on the arm now, which looks pretty rad;
28231|Her limbs are now roughly where they should be based on the previous shot;
28280|Two more shots of the statue before it's never seen or mentioned again;
28382|
28556|Celebratory redraw;
30308|Aside from being moved up, Shirley suffers only a very slight eye redraw;
30365|Trude has that line under her eye that makes her look tired and her chest is slightly less pointy;
30459|The lighting here is darker to match the other characters, and their heights are altered; 
31109|Miyafuji passing Perrine the letter is slower, they're both holding it for roughly twice as long before Perrine takes it;
31316|The illegible squiggles on the letter are replaced with <a title="so no difference, then">French</a>.
31345|Good Perrine;
31515|
32000|The back of the chair behind Perrine was fixed. Blessed image.
32411|Minna's pose is tighter and she's shaded darker;